Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da
What the fool
Actions that switch
I only spoke when I want to
Say I
with my spirit's name
Step down into a world I'm in
Shining on profits on parade
With the sun cracked open the matrix
And all my ghosts begin to fade
Hello, hello
Transmission cleared through the undertow
I'm feeling alive
Like a god turn the wheel and warp the air
Every glance of sacred fraud every breath of dare
A park beneath a watching moon the stars align they hum our tune the night unfolds our silver skin
We fall right through and start again
It's a dream
I'm feeling
It was a spark, not a throne
All I ever needed was a light to call my own
All I ever dreamed was someone new here
The voice in the dark say, you belong here
All I ever wanted was truth and ecstatic
A little bit of real in the world so dramatic
Can't my calm mother crowd through stone?
That saw me not the myth of the mass they all keep drawing the carnivals coming
But this time it's bright filled with misfits who learn to love the night
See I've been chained by my own reflection, but I burn those ropes divine insurrection now
I move clean through chaos and chatter gold from the madness. That's how come this matter
less your gift they laughed when I fell but I danced in the dirt every scar I
got just rewrote my worth all I ever wanted was to free my fear
You and ghosts with your halo dim
Airplane mode, I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing
not to be celestial but the way you left was biblical so i did something ritual
cause grief for me is silicone i might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
just to haunt you god damn head i knew you crave the chaos i fed
cause love like all they never did not to be divine but i love you
even when i want to curse you i could never
It's fair, every wound you gave I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my dream perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Not to be divine, but I love you
There's never spoken, every scar, a holy mark, every kiss, another spark
Not to be divine